<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resumes on Hannah Danks</title>
    <link>/resume/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resumes on Hannah Danks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/resume/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/resume/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/about-me/</guid>
      <description>About Me Canadian born, I was raised North of Dallas in Frisco, Texas. Having found a passion for taking care of animals early on, I have been driven throughout my education by the motivation to attend veterinary school and become a wildlife rescue veterinarian. I am currently in the application and interview process and am very excited for what’s in store!
Interests In my free time, I enjoying all things nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accomplishments</title>
      <link>/resume/accomplishments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/accomplishments/</guid>
      <description> Accomplishments  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/resume/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/education/</guid>
      <description> Education I have attended the University of Texas at Austin, where I will obtain a Bachelors in Science and Art in the Fall of 2019. My degree was focused in Biology with a study equivalent to a minor in Psychology. I have also received a Pre-Health Professions Certificate during this time.
Skills I have a base level knowledge of R Studio and Python.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Experience</title>
      <link>/resume/work-experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/work-experiences/</guid>
      <description> Work Experience I have worked as a kennel technician for over 350 hours at the Legacy Veterinary Hospital in Frisco, Texas, practicing skills such as medicating, expressing anal glands, and nail trims. I have worked as a technicians’ assistant since April of 2019 for Crestview Veterinary Clinic in Austin, Texas.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>